gazettextra.com 2004-06-06

# Terms of Use and Privacy Policy| The Janesville Gazette | Janesville, Wisconsin, USA

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
---|---|---|---|---  
|   
---  
  
|   
---  
SPECIAL SECTIONS  
FEATURED ADVERTISER  

|  |   
---|---  
  
|  |  |  **Terms of use** **PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING GAZETTEEXTRA.** By using this site, you signify your assent to these terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please do not use this site.

All materials appearing as part of GazetteExtra are protected by copyright as individual works and/or as a collective work or compilation under U.S. copyright and other laws and are property of Bliss Communications, Inc. or the party credited as the provider of the content.

Users of GazetteExtra shall not directly or indirectly copy, reproduce, transfer, distribute, publish, display, perform, modify, create derivative works, transmit or in any way exploit any content available through GazetteExtra, nor shall users distribute any part of GazetteExtra content over any network, sell or offer it for sale, or use such content to construct any kind of database. Users may download content from GazetteExtra for their own personal, non-commercial use but only if they make only one machine readable copy and/or one print copy. Users shall not alter or remove any copyright or other notice from copies of the content.

Associated Press (AP) news, photos, graphics, video, audio and other multimedia material accessed through GazetteExtra shall not be directly or indirectly reproduced, published, broadcast, sold, transferred, licensed, distributed in any manner or medium, used to prepare derivative works or displayed publicly in any manner or medium now known or later developed. AP news material may not be stored in whole or in part in a computer except for personal and non-commercial use. The AP will not be held liable for any delays, inaccuracies, errors or omissions in the AP service or in any AP material including without limitation any third-party content and any of the advertisement in the AP service or in the transmission or delivery of all or any part thereof or for any damages whatsoever.

**Privacy policy** We believe you have a right to know what personal information is collected during your visits to our web sites -- GazetteExtra.com, JanesvilleClassifieds.com and JanesvilleHomefront.com -- and how the information is used and safeguarded. You can view most of our content anonymously, but circumstances exist when information about you is collected. The information gathered falls into two categories: information you supply voluntarily and information we gather through technology.

**Information you supply voluntarily**

To use certain features and services on our web sites, you are asked to provide specific information about yourself. Examples of such features and services include submitting information for publication, entering contests, starting a print subscription, contacting us about a customer service problem, or subscribing to an email notifier. This information is collected when you fill out a browser-based form and is necessary to make the features useful and valuable. The forms have blank spaces into which you type the information. In most cases, we collect information such as your name, email address, telephone number, birth date and mailing address.

**How we use information you supply voluntarily**

We use the information you voluntarily supply to complete transactions or to communicate with you. For example, if you purchase a print subscription, we use your information to process your order. If you contact us for help, we use the information to contact you with a resolution to your problem or answer to your question. If you enter a contest, we use the information to determine eligibility and to contact winners. 

**Information gathered through technology**

Technology helps us gather other information. Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, which is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet. You likely enter the Internet through your Internet service provider, your company or your school. Your IP address does not identify you personally. Your email address is not collected through this process, and no data on your hard drive or personal or institutional servers are read.

We also collect aggregate information on how many people visit our sites and what pages people access on our sites. We do not track the specific pages that you or any individual access on our sites. Some of this information is gathered using a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie." The cookie does not identify you or other individual users. It merely identifies the computer you use. A cookie cannot read data on your hard drive or server or gather other personal information about you such as your name or email address.

**How we use information gathered through technology**

The information gathered through technology helps us make our sites more interesting and useful to you and other visitors. It helps us evaluate the value of and interest in specific sections of our sites. We can build better sites if we know which pages you and other people visit and how often you and others visit those pages.

**Sharing information with other parties**

Personal information you voluntarily provide is used for internal purposes only and is not shared with or sold to other businesses or organizations. Under no circumstances is specific information about you or other individuals shared with advertisers or other parties without your permission. Use of certain interactive features, such as submitting a restaurant review in our online dining guide, implies your permission to share your information. Situations where permission is implied are clearly labeled on the browser-based forms. We will share personal information with law enforcement officials as required under subpoena or court order to protect the safety and security of our sites, our visitors and the community. We do share aggregated statistics on site visits and page views with advertisers to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our web sites. Personal information about individuals is not shared with advertisers.

**Special notice to children**

Children should always get parental permission before sending any information about themselves over the Internet -- to us or anyone else. We encourage parents to review and share safety tips with their children using the Internet. Get information regarding our compliance with the Children's Online Privacy and Protect Act (COPPA). 

**Notice regarding other online companies**

The Janesville Gazette, Bliss Communications Inc. and Bliss New Media are affiliated with other online companies and providers, some of which feature our branding. Our web sites also provide text and graphic links to web sites over which we have no control or responsibility for content or business practices. This policy statement does not apply to the web sites of those companies and organizations. Please refer to these affiliated sites to obtain information on their privacy policies. If you cannot find the privacy policy of these sites via a link from the site's home page, you should contact the business or organization directly for more information.

**Our right to revise this policy**

The Internet is an ever-changing medium. We reserve the right to alter or amend this policy as required by changes in business strategy or developments in technology. If changes are required, we will post the changes before they go into effect. The use of information gathered while the current policy is in effect will be consistent with the current policy, even if we change the policy later.

**Questions or concerns**

Please send your questions and concerns about this policy to:

Grant M. VanderVelden  
Director of Online Services, The Janesville Gazette  
Manager, Bliss New Media  

|  |    
|  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
Home | [Business directory](http://www.blissnet.net/botw/index.html) | [Classifieds](http://www.janesvilleclassifieds.com/) | Contact us | [Dining guide](http://www.gazetteextra.com/diningout/main.html) | [Employment](http://www.gazetteextra.com/employment) | Local/state news  
National/world news | Newspapers in Education | [Personal ads](http://www.people2people.com/?connect=janesville) | [Real estate](http://www.janesvillehomefront.com/) | Subscribe   
Search engine powered by | [](http://www.google.com/)  
---|---  
  
Copyright ©2004 Bliss Communications Inc. All rights reserved.  
Use of this material and this site are subject to the GazetteExtra Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.   
Content may not be published, broadcast, re-distributed or re-written.
